Inventory of the Loring Phillips papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Loring Phillips papers
1917-1925
82011
Hoover Institution Archives
1 manuscript box, 1 envelope (0.5 linear feet)
Correspondence, orders, and photographs related to American military activities in the United States and France during World War I.
Phillips, Loring, 1895-1980.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1982.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
Second lieutenant, United States Army Quartermaster Corps.
Scope and Content of Collection
The collection contains correspondence, orders, and photographs related to American military activities in the United States and France during World War I. The collection is composed largely of personal correspondence between Loring Phillips and his parents.
United States Army. Quartermaster Corps.; United States. Army. American Expeditionary Forces.; World War, 1914-1918--Campaigns--France.
- Pamphlets, postcards, and telegrams, undated (Box-folder 1: 1)
- Correspondence, 1917-1925
  - Army correspondence, 1918-1925 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Miscellaneous letters to Phillips, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Letters to Phillips from his father, 1919 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Letters from Phillips to Mary, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Letters from Phillips to his mother, 1917 August 21-1921 December 26 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Letters from Phillips to his father, 1917 August 11-1919 August 4 (Box-folder 1: 7-9)
  - Undated letters from Phillips to his parents (Box-folder 1: 10)
- Photographs, 1918-1919
  - 12 prints depicting American and Allied military leaders and activities in France during World War I. (Envelope A)